CONTACT

julianepoma@gmail.com **Rosario**, Argentina

PROFILE

Julián is Software Engineer with a passion for learning and creating quality, functional code to solve problems. He enjoys designing projects and researching new technologies. His main interests are Web Development and aviation, and both complement each other really well.

LANGUAGES

Español - native Inglés - fluent, full professional proficiency

JULIÁN EMANUEL POMA

EXPERIENCE

Laravel 5 and VueJS 2 Developer SGC S.A

Rosario

December 2017 - Present

- In charge of the development of a lite-CRM system used to manage 5000 customers and the services offered.
- Managing the migration form the old databases.
- Development of a billing system and a customer's side application.

Web UI Bootcamp

Globant Rosario

May 2017 – June 2017

Learned the basics of web development, API requests and Single Page

Applications.

EDUCATION

Software Engineer

Universidad Tecnológica Rosario, Argentina April 2014 – December 2018 Relevant coursework:

- Data Mining
- Algorithms
- Web Development

Cambridge English First Certificate IATEL Rosario, Argentina

PERSONAL PROJECTS

BetterReads

Grade B

A fork of the known GoodReads, developed with the MEAN stack: MongoDB, Express and NodeJS serving a RESTful API, and Angular 6 providing the frontend. It offers full auth using JWT, files upload, protected routes and a material design style.

Fakestagram

A Progressive Web App clone of Instagram, which allows users to upload and share photos. It supports device camera access, localization and off-line synchronization.

SKILLS & KNOWLEDGE

Advanced
Laravel 5
VueJS 2
SQL Databases

Intermediate NodeJS MongoDB Google Firebase Angular 6

Basic Python PWAs

in /in/julianpoma

/julianpoma

